const STORE = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "Name the four basic instrument families",
    answers: {
      A: "Woodwinds, Strings, Brass, Percussion",
      B: "Winds, Metal, Shaker, Slappy",
      C: "Keyboard, Valve, Key, Contact",
      D: "Big, Small, Medium, over-easy"
    },
    correct: "Woodwinds, Strings, Brass, Percussion"
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question:
      "Which one of these instruments is a member of the Woodwind family?",
    answers: {
      A: "Trombone",
      B: "Harpsichord",
      C: "Viola",
      D: "Bassoon"
    },
    correct: "Bassoon"
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "Select the four main voice types",
    answers: {
      A: "Woman, Man, Boy, Girl",
      B: "Gravely, Smooth, piercing, flat",
      C: "Soprano, Alto, Tenor, Bass",
      D: "High, Low, Medium-High, Medium-Low"
    },
    correct: "Soprano, Alto, Tenor, Bass"
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "Which one of these voice types is the highest?",
    answers: {
      A: "Alto",
      B: "Contralto",
      C: "Mezzo-soprano",
      D: "Soprano"
    },
    correct: "Soprano"
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "Which one of the following is an element of music?",
    answers: {
      A: "Instruments",
      B: "Singing",
      C: "Dynamics",
      D: "Transposing"
    },
    correct: "Dynamics"
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "Which one of these terms is not typically found in music?",
    answers: {
      A: "Forte",
      B: "Largo",
      C: "Follemente",
      D: "Ritardando"
    },
    correct: "Follemente"
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "Which one of these musical periods is the earliest?",
    answers: {
      A: "Classical",
      B: "Baroque",
      C: "Modern",
      D: "Romantic"
    },
    correct: "Baroque"
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "Which one of these composers was born first?",
    answers: {
      A: "Johann Sebastian Bach",
      B: "Ludwig van Beethoven",
      C: "Igor Stravinsky",
      D: "John Philip Sousa"
    },
    correct: "Johann Sebastian Bach"
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: "How many symphonies did Beethoven write?",
    answers: {
      A: "3",
      B: "9",
      C: "48",
      D: "OVER 9000!!!!!!!"
    },
    correct: "9"
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question:
      "Which one of these instruments was used excessively in the band Jethro Tull?",
    answers: {
      A: "Clarinet",
      B: "Chainsaw",
      C: "Flute",
      D: "Flamethrower"
    },
    correct: "Flute"
  }
];

console.log(STORE);
